SERGIO RUIZ FULLSTACK JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER
FullStack JavaScript developer with 5° years industry experience, some the age of 6 with computers and since the age of 12 dealing with code, with strong skills in code quality, performance and continuous rinegration. Capacity to learn new languages and adeptablishy to new environments in not inter tharks to its overall showledge of languages and adeptablishy to revenivoronments in

### </> SKILLS

EEVELOPMENT HTMLS CSS3 LESS JAVASCRIPT REST AJAX GRUNT.JS

JAVASCRIPT JOUERY ANGULARJS VUE.JS REACTJS NODE.JS ZEPTO.JS UNDERSCORE

LODASH

LODASH

CI JENKINS SONAR GRUNT JS WEBPACK NPM UNIX DOCKER

DATABASES MYSQL SQLITE NOSQL MONGODB

SCM GIT GITHUB SVN TTS

SCM GIT GITHUB SVN TTS

SECURITY NAMAP NETCAT WIRESHARK ETTERCAP MSF NESSUS OPENVAS AIRCRACKNORTO

DESIGN PHOTOSHOP ZBRUSH SOFTIMAGE JXSI TERRAGEN GIMP 2 INKSCAPE

## EMPLOYMENT

Programmer Analyst, AURISAE

2013.12 — Present Software Developer at Teleforicas I-D. Yes worked mainly focused in full stack, jaesscript, continuous integration and evergetic HIMAL CSSS jaesdcript, but we guisely Select Science Check Scien

Systems integration Consulters: Programmers: 2012.01 — 2013.12

Systems integration Consulters: Programmers: 2012.01 — 2013.12

2013.01 — 2013.12

Programmer of System Integration In been developing a social interests, Android apps, rest services at BBNA GME project, sites with Google Sites or formed accumentations all MAM and Telestration Members and Section Section (Section Section Sec

# ★ PROJECTS

Creator; JS Test Lab An arcade machine lavaScript HTML5 CSS3

Agent Montain TV - Dith Hybrid September 1 -

Developer: Monitar IV - CO

2015-02 — 2015-03

Monitar IV web application, which allows to watch Live TV and VOD content, and handle your subscriptions, view the EPG and more, pioned the team for one month to speed development of new features.

January or Agella Month Service And Mind SCSS 3185 MAN Cell for this Scrum (ISA) Perfects Grunt is video vod pur

Main develope, Monitar TV. Chromosom Research
Chromosom
Chromo

Designor feeding: 2015.07 - 2016.02 (which application made with the magic of Meteor js and Lungs), connected to our internal LDAP server to handle light, which application made with the magic of Meteor js and Lungs), connected to our internal LDAP server to handle light, making friends of the Lungs js are printed at the Lungs js part to Ferior Louding blocks as some of the members of the team were members of Ferior G.S and wanted to see it in their devices. The pay allows to served feedback to people personally or anonymously about printed CSS plantaction.

single page application.

C# ASP.NET MVC 4 HTML5 CSS3 JavaScript Zepto js jQuery AJAX TFS

Developer, BBVA- Google App Engine (GAE) Team
Development of services and apps for BBVA using Google App Engine (GAE). After the development of services are days for BBVA using Google App Engine (GAE). After the development of several REST services are documentation weeks for internal projects using Google App Engine (GAE). After the development of several REST services (SAE) and Google App Engine REST gradiency (SAE) Google App Services (SAE). After the development of several REST services (SAE) and Google App Engine App Services (SAE).

Main developer, HEL: Android application

2012.02 — 2012.02 — 2012.02

Development of a tablet application (Android) for a pharmaceutical laboratory. This app is used to let pharmacists to fill and sign contracts of sile and exprintment with a pharmacy distabase. It captures the form as a digital image and stores the filled form in CVIs format to post process it.

Developer, TUYYOU - Development of a Social Network 2011-06 — 2012-06 Social network development using ELGG and modifying it's core. It was running for several years, being announced in several

### **EDUCATION**

Design and conceptualization of videogames; Imagina Formación
Course about design and conceptualization of videogames. It was about rewards, personalities, feedback, homo faber vs homo
Ludens, monetzation, causual players b nardocre players, (A) localization, equilibrium, interactive design...

Web development with Noole js, Imagina Formación
2016-09 — 2016-10
Noole js 54 course, with express, mongods, template engines like jade or Handlebars, using TDD with mocha, optimization with
Gruntjs, and deployment with Heroth.

Responsive Framework; Imagina Formación
2016-02 — 2016-04
Responsive Frameworks course using some frameworks like Base, Bootstrap and Foundation.

2015-12 — 2016-02

An introduction to literactive Programming in Python, Rice University 2013.01 – 2013.01

A course by Rice University of Courses, Carded with distriction. Integrational courses a criginated MORPH MINISTRATE.

Software development of Android devices Universitied National del Education a 2011.01 – 2012.01

Distancia: UNED

Android development, giving some hints about design and UX.

Engineering in Computer Science, Universidad Complutense de Madrid - UCM 2005-10 — 2010-12 Studied Engineering in Computer Science until 3rd grade, passed all programming practices.

# < AFFILIATION

Co-Organizer and member; MadridJS Meetup

Co-Organizer of MadridJS, helping with talks and organization but with the lack of time, just member since 2015

2012-02 — Present Member, javaScript study group
2011-08 — 2011-09
Study group formed by several members of the javaScript community in Madrid to learn and debate about javaScript
community in Madrid to learn and debate about javaScript

# SPEAKING

Game development in JavaScript, MadridJS Meetup 2012
It was a conference Carlos and I did about Game Development in JavaScript. It was in CAMON, with around 90 attendees. Here is the video, siders and Info about the session.

Workshop: Game programming in javaScript, GameMeS
Advanced workshop on how to develop a game without libraries, plain javaScript, for the GameMeS event. In this workshop we showed and explained in four hours, step by step, a shootem up demo. The game can be played here and the repo with more